♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
Where is my father?
Why aren't you with him?
You don't have a father! Okay?
Do you want Tatoy instead?
[Mercado] You have a follow-up mission.
[Atoy] This is the device I extracted
from the Zahran embassy, sir.
Why is it here again?
This laptop is for your safekeeping
until you find Ms. Lily Santiago,
who is in charge of this device.
[in English] You're the Master Cutter?!
Master Cutter, help us!
Oh, oh. No, I'm not.
We're administrators
of the Build for Kids organization.
The money we saved was stolen.
We'll try to contact another tracker.
Uh, maybe he can help you.
Please stop crying. Stop crying.
[Cita] Huh? Who?
- The… The son…
- [quirky sting]
Son of a thread.
[Atoy] Observe how the theft happened,
how they entered the place.
Just trust, and…
I'll bring them their karma.
[vendor] But Olga never told us
she had a missing child.
Don't talk to gossips.
Who else knows about the money here?
The ex-president of Build for Kids.
[Emerson] Kevin Martinez.
[Ame] You're acting
like the Master Cutter.
Atoy's level is way up here.
Yours is way down here!
[Kurt] Do you have a mission?
But Atoy isn't here, right?
PREVIOUSLY
[music swells]
♪ Fix this ♪
So, what? Let's go, girls?
[in English] Let's go.
["In Nothing" by Wickermoss
with Neth Macam playing]
It's safe now.
Why are we hiding from Cathy?
I'm just avoiding the issue.
I don't want Cathy and I
to fight because of you.
Because you're both important to me.
Really?
[music fades]
[suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[clacking]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
[gunshots]
[clicking]
[snipping]
[music swells]
[music fades]
[coughing]
What are you all doing here?
Why are you all crowding?
[T-bak] You're cold, huh?
The sun's blazing!
[chuckles]
I know. You're kissing!
No, we're not! Your mouth is sleazy.
I just said you're kissing,
I'm sleazy already?
Sleazy is being naked!
And besides, it's sweet!
No. I didn't kiss Karla.
- I have a girlfriend.
- [T-bak] Ouch.
Yes.
I'll just go see Cathy.
[gentle music playing]
That hurts.
- Shut up.
- [groans]
- You're irritating.
- [T-Bak] It hurts. [sighs]
Gavin, ouch.
[Denden] Uncle, where could Emerson be?
He's not at his shop.
And it's still not fixed.
- Oh.
- Maybe he moved?
He's with Atoy.
But don't bother him because
- he's frustrated.
- [in English] Because?
Because he's looking for someone.
But he doesn't know how to do it.
Is it a woman?
Oh, no, he's still looking
for someone else. I'm here, though.
Oh, Denden. Behave yourself!
You should play a little hard to get.
Like a Filipina maiden.
A Filipina maiden? How's that?
[Denden] Hard to get?
Will he like me if…
[suspicious music playing]
[Denden] I act like
a Filipina maiden, fine.
[dramatic sting]
[Denden] I'll learn how to be one.
[Denden giggles]
[dramatic stinging]
Uncle, you're not listening to me.
I've been talking nonstop.
Thank you.
Ah, brother, that man who just left.
Do you know him?
Ah, that's Boyet.
- Boyet.
- Yes, that's his place.
Ah, just there?
Just there.
[in English] Okay.
- [in English] Thank you.
- [Malou on the phone] Sir Emerson,
you called?
Any update on our case?
Uh, Ma'am Malou, yes, uh…
Well, um… Uh…
[Odette on phone] Did you catch the thief?
Was the money recovered?!
The son of the thread is amazing!
[in English] Wa, wa…
Wait, wait, wait. Wait, ma'am.
[titters] Uh, just relax.
Um, well, that's what
I wanted to tell you,
about the mission
and the son of the thread.
- Emerson! Emerson!
- [indistinct]
- It seems like… Wait… wait, wait, wait.
- [huffs]
This is important.
- Brother Kurt, I'm on the phone.
- [huffs]
It's about your mission!
- [Emerson] Wha-- What?
- I saw the thief on the CCTV!
- [Kurt] Yes!
- How--
How can you be sure?
I saw it in the footage.
He stretched his hands in a strange way.
And… [chuckles]
the diamond tattoos on his fingers!
Oh, didn't you notice that?
Uh, what? I noticed them too.
Hmm, you. I was
just testing you, of course.
Anyway, I saw that man
at the fishball stand earlier,
and I know where he's going.
- Ah. Mm-hmm.
- Really? Really?
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Yes.
Yes. Hello, he… Ma'am? Ma'am? Hello.
Ah, Ma'am Malou, yes.
Here's the update.
We have a lead. [chuckles]
So, just relax, ma'am.
Sit tight, and the son of the thread
will handle this.
[in English] Okay, ma'am? All right!
Thank you! Bye-bye.
[giggles]
Awesome, awesome. Okay.
Let's go. Let's check it out.
This is exciting.
It's like we're…
I'm Atoy, and you're the sidekick.
Why am I the sidekick?
I found the suspect!
That was just luck!
I'll show you later,
I'll handle the strategy.
[in English] I'll show you.
Let's go. Let's check it out.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
[sneaky music playing]
That's where Boyet works.
That's what the fishball vendor said.
[in English] Oh, affirmative.
Looks like this is our suspect.
So, what's our next step?
[in English] Hmm, call a friend.
[music fades]
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
What now?
[in English] Good news.
We found the suspect
in the theft of five million.
[smirks] Nice, huh.
[in English] Okay.
In fairness, you're good.
Of course. You know me.
Ah, Atoy, Atoy! This is Brother Kurt.
I'm the one who found him.
This is Brother Kurt.
Fine. Ah, fine, fine.
Brother Kurt?
[smirks] That explains it.
But I'm wondering, Atoy,
if he has five million,
why is he still vulcanizing at that shop?
[suspicious music playing]
Because if it were me, I'd buy a fancy car
and a nice house.
I would just relax.
YOLO, right?
That means the five million isn't his.
He's giving the money to someone else.
[in English] My thoughts exactly.
Oh, so you're the best.
[Atoy on phone] Here's what you do.
The important thing to do
is go to that shop.
[Atoy on phone] Pretend to be customers
or whatever you want.
The important thing is, get inside,
and gather information
about the money from that person.
Just make sure you don't get detected.
- [in English] G.
- [in English] Okay.
Let's go.
Here's the plan.
I'll be Mateo.
I'm the new up-and-coming race car driver.
I'll use an Italian accent.
Um…
[in Italian accent] Goodbye. Goodbye.
- Hmm?
- Feels like I need a mustache.
Oh. You even have a backstory?
But you forgot the most important part.
What?
We need a tire to vulcanize.
[sneaky music playing]
- Wow. Impressive.
- Right?
[in English] Very good.
I was just testing
if you really learned from Atoy.
[in English] Hmm. But…
Where are we going to get the bike tire?
[clicks tongue]
- So, we'll think of a way…
- [Karla] Brother! How are you?
- What are you doing here?
- [Emerson mutters]
[in Italian] Silence. Silence.
Uh, hmm…
Aha!
Oh, give me the ball.
Hmm?
[Karla] What are you going to do?
[Emerson] Just trust me.
Hey, brother! I just bought that!
That ball was expensive!
- [hushing]
- [in Italian] Understood. Understood.
I'll replace it later.
We need it for our operation
surveillance, care of the children
of the thread.
Surveillance? Are you pretending
to be monsters?
Who are the children of the thread?
Just keep quiet.
Just keep quiet. Don't…
[barista, in English]
Cafe Americano for Atoy.
- [barista, in English] Americano for Atoy.
- Atoy?
- [man, in English] Good morning.
- [barista, in English] Atoy, sir?
[in English] Yes.
[Atoy, in English] Thank you.
[pensive music playing]
[Samir, in English] Ms. Audrey.
[music fades]
[in English] Samir, from the embassy.
[in English] Yes, I remember.
[in English] Samir, hi.
[in English] May I?
Um…
[suspicious music playing]
[clears throat]
[music fades]
There, Italian. Got it.
[clears throat]
[in Italian] Hello. Goodbye.
[in Spanish] Hasta la vista! [titters]
[speaking indistinctly in a vague accent]
Um, Mateo.
Pa-- Patch! No, um, uh--
The… The hole. The… The strong kick!
[stuttering]
The ball, the hole, ah… patch!
[smirks, in Italian] Yes.
[Emerson, in Italian] Yes.
- Hmm…
- [Emerson] Hmm?
- [in Italian] Fifty.
- [in Italian] Fifty?
Too expensive.
No, I'm Filipino too.
- And can't you lower it to 30?
- [quirky sting]
- Fine.
- [Emerson] You can?
Okay, 30.
[in Italian] Goodbye.
[chuckles]
[in Italian] Yes.
[sneaky music playing]
[Emerson] Oh, ah! See, uh, hmm.
- Diamond.
- [Boyet chuckles]
- [chuckles]
- Truly diamond.
Ah, tattoo.
- [phone ringing]
- [suspicious music playing]
[Boyet grunts]
- Wait a moment.
- [chuckles]
- [in Italian] Yes, uh…
- [in English] Hello, boss!
Yes. Your suitcase is here.
‪[dramatic sting, music intensifies]
[in English] Hello, boss.
Your suitcase is here.
The money is safe, don't worry.
[inhales, grunts]
[Boyet] If you want, boss,
I can even take a picture of it.
[clicks tongue] Don't worry.
I won't steal from you.
So, boss? Do you want me to count it?
By the way, boss, where are we meeting?
Yes! I'm not stupid.
[music fades]
Ten o'clock in the morning.
7176!RbSbOlive Function Hall,
Athena Hotel.
[suspicious music playing]
As long as my share is complete, boss,
we won't have any problem.
‪[sniffles]
[music concludes]
[Boyet] Who's there?
Come out if you don't want to get hurt.
[music swells]
Who's there?!
[tense music playing]
[Kurt] Oh!
Hello!
Uh, who are you?
[in English] Ah, I come in peace.
I'm not a bad person.
[in English] Actually,
I'm a vlogger. [chuckles]
- [Boyet, in English] Vlogger.
- [Kurt, in English] Yes.
[ominous music playing]
[Boyet] What do you need?
Well, I just wanted to feature your shop.
It looks great.
Uh, what do you do here?
Who are your usual customers?
- [Boyet chuckles]
- [indistinct]
- [Boyet] Yes, yes.
- [Kurt] We'll feature everything!
[Boyet] Those rims are cheap.
- They look great.
- Tomorrow, the branded ones will arrive.
Wow, so many rims here, bro.
Game!
But wait.
Is there a fee for this?
Fee?
None.
Just a shout-out.
[in English] Shout-out?
Fine, you may leave now.
- Ah, okay.
- You're wasting my time.
[in English] Okay. Sorry, sorry.
[in English] Thank you for your time.
[tense music playing]
[suspicious music playing]
Brother Kurt, thank you so much earlier.
You saved me there.
Boyet really looked ready
to pull something shady.
- Oh, it's nothing!
- Come on!
Well, you disappeared for so long.
I thought you got into trouble.
[Emerson] Mmm.
Did you get anything
from risking your life there?
Of course!
I saw the five million myself
inside the suitcase.
- [in English] Five million?!
- Yes!
Incredible!
He said he'll turn it over tomorrow,
at the Athena Hotel, Olive Function Room.
[in English] At 10 a.m.
Let me check.
[in English] Mm, Athena Hotel.
That's it, brother.
There's an auction tomorrow morning.
At the Olive Function Room.
That's it, that's it.
That's where Boyet will go tomorrow.
That's where he'll meet his Boss KM.
Boss KM, Boss KM.
- Who could that be?
- Ouch.
[suspicious music playing]
That woman, Ms. Odette,
mentioned something.
She said their former president's name
was Kevin…
Martinez!
Kevin Martinez. That's his name.
- Kevin Martinez.
- [Emerson] Mm-hmm.
KM. So, he's Boss KM!
- Oh, right.
- [Karla] Right?!
[in English] Very good!
Very good, you're right!
He might really be
the mastermind behind the theft.
You're amazing.
[Ame] Oh, no.
We need to get the money from Boyet
before he gives it to KM!
How?
- [Kurt] Oh, call a friend again!
- Mmm, mmm, mmm.
[Emerson] Enough, enough.
I know.
I got it.
- [smirks]
- [action music playing]
[line rings]
[in English] You look
as beautiful as ever.
[in English] Thank you. Um…
[in English] I'm just dressed up today,
because I'm actually waiting
for my boyfriend.
[pensive music playing]
[in English] Uh, you don't have
a boyfriend.
[in English] One coffee, one fork.
[in English] Just you.
[in English] What if he doesn't like cake?
[in English] Look, maybe
we got off on the wrong foot.
[in English] Uh, with the embassy and me
accusing you of stealing and breaking in.
[in English] So, I'm sorry for that.
[in English] So, does that mean that
I'm not a suspect anymore?
[in English] You are not a suspect,
no, no.
[in English] We actually have
a picture of the suspect.
- [in English] Really?
- [Samir, in English] Yes.
- [in English] How?
- [Samir clears throat, in English] AI.
[in English] My men got footage from CCTV,
and then we made a picture using AI.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] This man
is a master of disguise.
[in English] He pretended to be
a window cleaner
to sneak into the embassy.
[music swells]
[in English] Do you know this man?
[tense music playing]
[music intensifies]
[Audrey, in English] No, no, no.
I… I got-- I got it.
[Audrey clears throat]
[pensive music playing]
[in English] I'm sorry,
I'm… [chuckles] so embarrassed.
[in English] I'm usually not this clumsy.
[in English] It's not because you maybe
recognized this man?
[in English] No. No, I don't know him. Um…
[in English] You mentioned
that it's AI-generated, right?
- [in English] Yes.
- [in English] So, doesn't that mean that
there's a chance that maybe
the composition is wrong?
[in English] I mean, come on.
[in English] He's too handsome
to be a thief.
[in English] He looks more
like a model, an actor.
[in English] You know Dingdong Dantes?
[in English] Never heard of that man.
[in English] But, um… maybe you're right.
[in English] Or maybe you're wrong.
[in English] Anyway,
it was nice talking to you,
but I really have to go.
[in English] Um, Ms. Audrey, maybe, um…
I can have your phone number?
[in English] I can invite you
to some events at the embassy.
[in English] I really
don't want to go back there
after the robbery at the embassy,
- and I'm still traumatized.
- [in English] Yes. How about, um…
[in English] Maybe
we can go exercise, running?
[in English] Uh, sometimes I go running
in the Acacia Grove on Saturday.
[in English] You've been there?
[in English] No, never.
[in English] Um… But yes, sure.
[in English] Why not?
[in English] I mean, I gotta go. Okay?
[in English] It was…
It was nice chatting with you.
[in English] Ms. Audrey.
[tense music playing]
[in English] Your phone number.
[in English] Oh, I'm sorry. I… I forgot.
‪Um…
[in English] There you go.
[in English] I gotta go.
- [Samir, in English] Goodbye.
- [in English] Bye!
[music swells]
[music fades]
[muffled chattering in the distance]
[in English] Hello, everybody!
[Atoy, in English] So, I see
no other way for you
to intercept the package,
but for you to be present at the auction.
Wow, your voice is making me swoon, Atoy!
[in English] Ame, this is serious.
[in English] Your mission
is to retrieve the package
with the five million pesos in it.
[Atoy] Let's assume the auction venue
is heavily guarded.
Of course, because
expensive items will be there.
[in English] Uh, copy that, Atoy.
[Atoy] Someone needs to pose
as a buyer attending the auction.
You need to look rich.
The type who can spend millions
on a single item.
But not all of you can be buyers.
Some of you need to be the eyes and ears.
[Atoy] And of course, someone
must be assigned as a distraction
if things don't go according to plan.
[in English] Copy?
We know what you mean, Atoy.
We can handle this.
[in English] Very good.
By the way, how many of you are there?
Who's with you?
Uh…
Me, Ame, Brother Kurt,
and Karla, and we are the…
Children of the Thread.
See? It's good, right?
Nice, right? It's nice. I thought of it.
I thought of it.
Fine, fine.
- All right.
- I thought of it.
- We'll give it to you.
- Hmm.
Did you say Karla?
[Kurt] Why not?
The more the merrier.
Don't bring Karla.
[pensive music playing]
Hey. Oh, Karla!
Uh, um…
Okay, ‘Toy…
I'll handle it.
We'll fix this. We'll update you.
[in English] Okay.
[pensive music playing]
[Emerson] Karla.
Poor Karla.
I told you.
Hey. Are you okay?
Of course not. You walked out.
I was happy for a moment.
I heard Brother Atoy's voice.
At least I knew he was safe. He's okay.
But is he really that upset with me?
He barred me from the mission?
You're too sensitive.
[melancholic music playing]
[Emerson] Look.
You know…
I understand Atoy
because he's your brother.
If it were me…
If Tonet were here,
I wouldn't let her join
dangerous missions either.
I don't want her to get hurt.
She's my sister. I love her.
But if Sis Tonet were here,
she'd want you to be together, right?
At least you'd be sure you're both safe.
[pensive music playing]
Please, brother.
Include me, please.
I don't want to be left behind,
just worrying about you.
I promise, I can help.
You're so persistent.
I'll get scolded by Atoy.
He'll be mad at me.
Here's the plan, brother.
Let's not tell Brother Atoy.
He doesn't need to know, right?
[suspicious music playing]
Come on, I'll help.
[electronic blipping]
[tense music playing]
Do we really need suspenders?
It's our brand identity!
We need to look solid
for our first mission.
Operation Suitcase.
Is Atoy here?
I wanted to ask permission from him.
We're going to the US.
- Vacation?
- [in English] Maybe for good.
[screaming and panicking]
[thumping and groaning]
UP NEXT
No kids allowed here.
Help me. They're going to kill my mom!
Mama!
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
[grunts]
[security officer, in English]
Our intel told us
that the decoder of this town
is the mayor's niece.
[in English] So, she might be here.
[in English] This is the man who
brought him to the ambassador's office.
[Samir, in English] Here.
He might be here too.
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
♪ Fix this ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias